FormRuins ^{
	WB ^{
        Leader ^{
            Greeting=Hello, <Player>! You are already quite a celebrity in this Galaxy and one of its most intrepid pilots. Know that you will always receive the warmest welcome here at the <WB> military base.
            NewRank=Congratulations! According to our scale your piloting experience already corresponds to the next rank. You are now a <Rank>, one of the best pilots in the Galaxy. Know that you will always receive the warmest welcome here at the <WB> military base.
			NewRank=In the meantime, please accept this <ItemName> from us as a token of our gratitude for your accomplishments in the line of fire. Oh, and by the way - I assume you've already dealt with our secret camouflage devices that allow you to perfectly disguise your ship as a dominator? If not, then it's okay - it will still have time. Right now we are putting at your disposal a personal naval electronic signature, with which you will be able to identify your ship in front of any coalition pilot, even without removing your camouflage. Convenient, right? By the way, the recognition system works automatically on all our military vessels, so their own will not touch you now anyway. Well, good hunting, <Rank>!
        }
	}
}

Script ^{
    Mod_EvoComfyCamo ^{
		0=<0>
	
		PlayerSendSignature1=Calm down, you sicky! I'm just working undercover, that's my military signature...
		PlayerSendSignature2=Hey-hey, be quiet! Pour some valerian into your tank, psychonaut! I'm not some kind of machine for you, but the very defender of the Galaxy - that's the proof...
		PlayerSendSignature3=Calm down! Put aside the panic, don't drop the bricks! A secret agent <Player> is on duty - here is my electronic Id...
		PlayerSendSignature4=Recover, you nutcase! I'm the operative, don't you see? Here is an electronic pass...
		PlayerSendSignature5=If I were a dominator, do you think I would talk to you, blockhead? Here's my electronic signature - run it through the database, loony...

		OnReceiveSignature1=Oh, what?! Seriously!? Ranger <Player>??
		OnReceiveSignature1=Damn, man! Well, you scared the hell out of me. Are you already completely out there from impotence, have you gone mad?! So after all, you can bring it to a heart attack. I added your Id to the trusted list, you won't fool me with your tricks anymore.
		//
		OnReceiveSignature2=WHAT!?!
		OnReceiveSignature2=...
		OnReceiveSignature2=Okay, I got it, I realized. Now I'm finishing my business and urgently taking a long vacation. Well, whatever all these "spy quirks" of yours.
		//
		OnReceiveSignature3=AHAHAHA!!! Oh, I can't! Well, you give, warriors! Ahaha! Is this like - can't win - lead?! AHAHAHA!!!
		OnReceiveSignature3=...
		OnReceiveSignature3=[Caller disconnected]
		//
		OnReceiveSignature4=Oh, you silicone bastard!!! Trying to fool m... Oh, damn. Seems you are tryle a ranger, don't you?
		OnReceiveSignature4=...
		OnReceiveSignature4=It's the first time I've seen this, to be honest. Well, how is it there - to live in the skin of a dominator? Boring, isn't it? Fly yourself through a dead system, rounding circles, no one to chat with. Oh, loneliness...
		//
		OnReceiveSignature5=Damn me! What technology has come to during the war! In that case, I beg your pardon, and I wish you good luck in freeing the Galaxy from this steel infection.
	}
}

ShipInfo ^{
    AddInfo ^{
        CustomInfos ^{
			IgnoreCamoInfo ^{
				Name=Корабли с этой маркерной инфошкой будут адекватно реагировать на игрока в камуфляже
                Description=NoShow
                Icon=0
				
				//Data1 - если != 0, то такому кораблю мод EvoYouDontFoolMe не накинет дополнительных текстов в приветственный текст
			}
		}
	}
}