FormIntroduction ^{
    MCW1=Creating the Galaxy
    MCW2=Creating stars
    MCW3=Creating planets
    MCW4=Distributing quests
    MCW5=Coalition ships and dominators
    MCW6=Creating bases
    MCW7=Passage of time
    MCW8=Done

    Text=<clr><clrEnd>    Volunteers! You have made the right choice by joining the glorious ranger ranks! Battleship and dreadnought crews may take pride in their fancy uniforms, but in the Klissan War three hundred years ago, as they suffered one defeat after another, it was the rangers who solved the mystery of Makhpella and put an end to the most terrible war in the history of this sector of the Galaxy! The rangers are no cannon fodder, capable only of obeying orders; every ranger is his own general and supply battalion!
    Text=<br>    Admittedly, over the centuries many have forgotten the rangers' noble history and customs. But there's no better time to remind them! As you know, six years ago the Coalition of intelligent races has encountered a new enemy -- an enemy no less dangerous than the klissan. They are called the dominators and represent a new form of cyberlife. As of yet, we do not know why they have begun attacking us, both on our planets and in space. Most dominator robots have only a semblance of intelligence, so it stands to reason they are controlled by brain centers. Initially it was believed that they had only one such center, but this presumption proved a costly mistake for the Coalition fleet at the Battle of Gralgar! Now we know that there is a minimum of three such centers, each controlling its own series of dominators. The earthlings who discovered this called these series "blazer", "keller" and "terron".
    Text=<br>    We were able to learn the origin of these robots and some things about their inner workings, but this information is classified. Perhaps you will be granted access to it at a later date. Besides, now is not the time for lectures -- the dominators have already captured tons of planets, and our fleet is still struggling to recover from the Gralgar massacre! This means that space rangers have once again become our last hope for survival. And now the only thing keeping you from eternal glory is a medical examination. But between you and me, due to the desperate situation on both fronts, the doctors were given a secret directive to give all candidates a clean bill of health! Dismissed, soldier!
}
Script ~{
    MS_Begin ^{
        64=On behalf of the Interstellar Coalition and the <0> Ranger Center in particular, I would like to thank all the true patriots enrolling into the ranger force in this hour of hardship! We all remember that more than two hundred years ago it was the rangers who put an end to the Klissan War that threatened the very existence of all five Coalition civilizations. That war was a lesson to us all, strengthening the unity of the Coalition. Thanks to this war, whatever misunderstandings arose in the last two centuries were resolved swiftly and peacefully. This long-standing peace was broken six years ago when unidentified aggressors attacked a science expedition from Earth in a remote star system. Nobody survived.
		64=Thus the Coalition met a new terrible enemy. War machines of unknown design that self-reproduce at a rapid pace, taking over one system after another, fighting with equal skill on planets, in open space and in hyperspace. The earthlings from the first encounter had named them dominators. Alas, despite the heroism of our military, the attempt to crush the enemy in one fell swoop at the Battle of Gralgar proved disastrous. As we suffered tremendous losses, the dominators were able to withdraw their brain center -- <clr>Blazer<clrEnd> -- from the main strike. At present they are continuing to reproduce on unknown bases in remote space. Since then, the situation has become increasingly difficult. Some alarmists claim that we are losing this war so it's even more gratifying to see your patriotism and will to win!
        65=Would you like to complete a ranger training course first? This is a unique possibility to learn the basics of navigation, shooting, handling cargo and conducting trade absolutely free!
		10=We are happy to provide you with all the knowledge a ranger needs. Your first mission will be a simple one -- take off from the ranger center and land on your home planet of <0>. An experienced instructor will be waiting for you at the spaceport.
		73=<0>
    }
    MS_SB1 ^{
		12=Get information about dominators at the <0> research station.//Quest
        0=Ah, <Player>. It's the same old story -- first you enlist, then you start wondering who it is we're fighting?
        6=Rangers are not part of the regular army//Player
        1=But none of that matters... What matters is that you're trying to use brute force where it's better to sit and think hard on the matter...
        22=There's no time to think! Dominators and pirates are attacking us across all known space!//Player
		2=Sure, thinking is what we do... Very well, here's your orientation. By the way, what is your clearance level? Oh, right, you're a rookie, which means it's basic. Dominators are a new non-organic life-form. As with the klissan, they comprise interchangeable micromodules, capable of forming various configurations. After all, the klissan "protoplasm" isn't actually a protoplasm, but a myriad of microcrystals... It's the same with the dominators, only their modules are larger and less mobile, while each one is capable of handling a greater variety of functions. The earthlings called these modules <clr>nodes<clrEnd>, and if used correctly they could be used to upgrade our own technologies. Your rank and file dominators are only pseudo-intelligent, but the coordination and success with which they fight suggest there's a brain center somewhere controlling them. It was initially theorized that there was one such center and that it was located on Gralgar, but that was a mistake which cost us dearly...
        8=There must have been two of them, then?!//Player
        26=Now we know there are at least three such centers, each of which is controlling its own dominator series. The centers were codenamed <clr>Blazer<clrEnd>, <clr>Keller<clrEnd> and <clr>Terron<clrEnd>. Their series are called accordingly, minus the capitalization. All three are hostile toward us, though we still do not know why. There are also differences between them, however. Blazeroids are the most aggressive and wield the most powerful and varied weaponry. According to our intelligence, Blazer himself is based somewhere in space and does not land on planets. Kelleroids are the most progressive technologically. Their use of hyperspace, for instance, is especially masterful. It appears that they're utilizing the "bubbles" method that had been once used by gaals and Makhpella. We believe that Keller himself resides in one such bubble and never actually appears in regular space. And then there's Terron, of whom we know very little. He appears to be based somewhere very remote, and we only ever meet the front lines of his army. The information we've managed to extract from captured terronoids suggests he may be based on the surface of a planet somewhere. If only we knew what he was up to... But then, any new information we get is very important for us. Deliver your trophies to research stations and we will supply you with our newest technologies.
        9=Understood. But do we know where the dominators come from?//Player
        4=This is all the information allowed by your clearance. Information about the origins of the dominators is classified and strictly guarded by the war ministry. Privates have no right to it. You may return once you've gained a new military rank. And to do that you first need to upgrade your ship, buy an engine and a few good shooters. Did they teach you trade yet?
        23=They have. I know how to earn a living.//Player
        25=So that's great. Now you should make money, fight the dominators and earn military ranks. In the meantime, we can tell you about our network of research stations.
		11=Very well, tell me//Player
        27=Our network of stations has spread across the entire Galaxy over the last three centuries. The most brilliant minds of the Interstellar Coalition are here, laboring to crack the great mysteries of the Universe. At present we are highly concerned with the military advances of the dominators, and we're looking for technologies to stop them.
		27=We have orders from the Interstellar Coalition Council to help the rangers as best we can. We are ready to repair and upgrade your ship at the lowest possible prices.
    }
}
// FormGameSet2 ^{
    // Common ^{
        // LevelGroup1=Dominators
        // NameGroup1Easy=Weak
        // NameGroup1Normal=Ordinary
        // NameGroup1Hard=Strong
        // NameGroup1Expert=Tough
        // HelpGroup1Easy=Dominators are weaker than Coalition forces
        // HelpGroup1Normal=Dominators and Coalition forces are equal
        // HelpGroup1Hard=Dominators are stronger than Coalition
        // HelpGroup1Expert=Dominators are much stronger than Coalition
    // }
// }